Andre Agrippa

4 Rollo Drive ◆ Ajax, Ontario L1S 7E7 ◆ (289) 892-6142

E-mail: andreagrippa76@gmail.com LinkedIn: linkedin.com/in/andre-agrippa-6255381aa

https://github.com/vans12345678

Summary

I have been interested in computers and programming for several years. I am experienced with object-oriented programming (Java, C++, C#, Vb.NET), Web development (PHP, ASP.NET, HTML, CSS, SQL), GUI, and the SDLC framework. I am looking to put my knowledge in programming to the test and apply what I have learned over the years in the workforce.

Education

2019 - Present: Currently enrolled at Durham College for Computer Programmer Analyst

2018: Université de Montréal Level 4 French Explore Program

2013 - 2017: Graduate student of Ajax High School (Grade 12)

2013 - Present: Strong ability using Microsoft Word, Excel, PowerPoint, Internet to conduct research, computer hardware and components, Object-Oriented Programming (Java, C++, C#, Vb.NET), Web Development(HTML, CSS, PHP, ASP.NET, SQL) Bash and shell scripting.

2005 - Present: Fluent in French (High School Bilingual Certificate; fluent in English and French)

Work Experience

2019-Present: Costco Ajax

- Customer Service Representative
- Majors Department
- Cashier

2015 – 2020: OMHA Referee – Ajax, Pickering, Whitby Locations (House League and Rep Games)

- Enforce rules and regulations
- Establish rapport with coaches and other referees
- Compile scores
- Maintain safety of players
- Working in a team-based system

Achievements

2019-Present: Durham College - Honour Roll

2015: Recipient of the Brian English Scholarship (OMHA Referee School)

2013: Volunteer at Westminster United Church Camp with kid's age 4-11 years old